Guide to the Solomon Sir Jones Films
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Solomon Sir Jones films
1924-1928
WA MSS S-2636
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
0.2
(29 reels)
The Solomon Sir Jones films consist of 29 silent black and white films documenting African-American communities in Oklahoma from 1924 to 1928. Jones filmed Oklahoma residents in their homes; during their social, school and church activities; in the businesses they owned; and performing various jobs. The films document several Oklahoma communities, including Muskogee, Okmulgee, Tulsa, Wewoka, Bristow and Taft. The films also document Jones's trips to Indiana, Texas, Louisiana, Arkansas, Tennessee, Missouri, Illinois, New York City, South Carolina, Colorado, and overseas to France, England, Palestine, Switzerland, Italy, Northern Africa, and Germany. Slates between scenes identify locations, dates, and subjects. The films measure 12,800 feet (355 min).
29 reels: motion picture film 16mm.
Jones, Solomon, Sir, 1869-1936
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Swann Galleries on the Frederick W. and Carrie S. Beinecke Fund for Western Americana, 2009.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
All original and surrogate films are restricted and may be consulted only with permission of the appropriate curator. Each film is available as digital video in the Beinecke Library's Digital Images Online database; links are provided at the film level. DVD reference copies are available in Box 1 listed at the end of the finding aid.
Existence and Location of Copies
Each film has a corresponding 16mm negative, 16mm fine grain master print, and various digital file formats.
Solomon Sir Jones (1869-1936)
Solomon Sir Jones, Baptist minister, businessman, and amateur filmmaker. Jones was born in Tennessee to former slaves and grew up in the South before moving to Oklahoma in 1889. Jones became an influential Baptist minister, building and pastoring fifteen churches. He was head of the Boyd Faction of Negro Baptists in America and was a successful businessman.
Scope and Contents
The Solomon Sir Jones films consist of 29 silent black and white films documenting African-American communities in Oklahoma from 1924 to 1928. The films measure 12,800 feet (355 min). All films are B-wind positive prints, except one roll that contains approximately 150 feet of orange base B-wind positive.
Jones filmed Oklahoma residents in their homes; during their social, school and church activities; in the businesses they owned; and performing various jobs. The films document several Oklahoma communities, including Muskogee, Okmulgee, Tulsa, Wewoka, Bristow and Taft. The films also document Jones's trips to Indiana, Texas, Louisiana, Arkansas, Tennessee, Missouri, Illinois, New York City, South Carolina, Colorado, and overseas to France, England, Palestine, Switzerland, Italy, Northern Africa, and Germany. Slates between scenes identify locations, dates, and subjects.
Jones frequently filmed at various locations by positioning himself outside a building while people exited the building in a line. This perspective provides footage of people as they walk by the camera, usually looking directly at it. Footage of churches includes congregants exiting the service and socializing outside; footage of schools often includes students playing outside or doing exercises; and footage of people at their home includes them outside on their porches or in their yards. Aside from church and scheduled school activities, people presumably exited at Jones's request for the purpose of being filmed by him.
Arrangement
Arranged numerically by film number assigned before Yale's 2009 acquisition.
African American families; African Americans; African Americans -- Oklahoma; African Americans -- Social life and customs; African American Baptists -- Oklahoma; African American business enterprises -- Oklahoma; African American churches -- Oklahoma; Oklahoma -- Social life and customs; Oklahoma -- Muskogee; Oklahoma -- Okmulgee; United States -- Description and travel; Audiovisual materials; Motion pictures (visual works); Home movies; Travelogs; Jones, Solomon, Sir, 1869-1936
- Original films
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. For further information consult Access Services.
  - Film 1, 1925, undated; (401 feet) (Box 1 (Original))
    Scope and Contents note
    Shrinkage 1.3-1.5%, 47 splices, many ripped perforations, some burned frames, several sections with pulled perforations on both sides, some taped splices, some torn frames.
    Time codes correspond to digital video reference copies.
    - Congregationalists coming out of church, Clearview, OK, 1925; 00:00:00 - 00:01:02
    - Melvin School, District No. 57, Clearview, OK, 1925; 00:01:03 - 00:01:19
    - C. S. and B. College of General Baptist State Convention of Oklahoma, Clearview, OK, 1925; 00:01:20 - 00:02:11
    - Woodman of Union 4000, Members B. Driae, Needham Betley, Special Representative, Muskogee, OK, 1925 July 13; 00:02:12 - 00:02:39
    - First Baptist Church of Guthrie erected by Dr. S. S. Jones, 1898 to 1905, Guthrie, OK, 1925; 00:02:40 - 00:02:54
    - Langston University, Honorary J. W. Young President, Graduation Ceremony, Langston, OK, 1925 May; 00:02:55 - 00:05:22
    - Mr. and Mrs. George W. Davis, country home, 20 miles from Muskogee, OK, 1925; 00:05:23 - 00:06:01
    - His herd bulls, Aberdeen, Angus, Herford, Muskogee, OK, 1925; 00:06:02 - 00:06:23
    - Coming from the city, Muskogee, OK, 1925; 00:06:24 - 00:06:42
    - Russell Davis Farm No. 1, Muskogee, OK, 1925; 00:06:43 - 00:06:55
    - His alfalfa farm, Muskogee, OK, 1925; 00:06:56 - 00:07:22
    - Russell Davis Farm No. 3, Muskogee, OK, 1925; 00:07:23 - 00:07:34
    - Mrs. George Davis Farm, two girls with sunhats, Muskogee, OK, 1925; 00:07:35 - 00:07:51
    - Russell Davis Farm No. 2, Muskogee, OK, 1925; 00:07:52 - 00:08:04
    - First part of his thoroughbred cattle, Angus herd, Muskogee, OK, 1925; 00:08:05 - 00:08:51
    - Mrs. George Davis Herford cattle, Muskogee, OK, 1925; 00:08:52 - 00:09:15
    - Second part of their Angus herd, Muskogee, OK, 1925; 00:09:16 - 00:10:05
    - Mr. Davis and some of his cowboys after the round-up, Muskogee, OK, 1925; 00:10:06 - 00:10:25
    - The end of the punching, undated; 00:10:26 - 00:10:38
    - Unidentified home and individuals, undated; 00:10:39- 00:11:35
    - Mr. and Mrs. L. E. Ragsdale first farm home near Bristow, OK, 1925; 00:11:36 - 00:11:49
    - Their No. 5 1000 Barrel Oil Well; their number 4 gusher near the poor farm, their number 1 4000BL per day oil well, Bristow, OK, 1925; 00:11:50 - 00:13:44
    - Coming from the city, Bristow, OK, 1925; 00:13:45 - 00:14:11
    - Lincoln High School, Professor G. H. Kaynon, Principal, Bristow, OK, 1925 October 13; 00:14:12 - 00:14:59
  - Film 2, 1927, undated; (464 feet) (Box 2 (Original))
    Scope and Contents
    Shrinkage 0.9-1.3, 22 splices, few torn frames, few ripped perforations.
    - Unidentified people at a house; cars coming off river barge; people exiting a residence and playing a game outside; unidentified school; children filing into school with teachers; children in a circle playing hokey-pokey, wrestling, and on a see-saw; women on the porch of a residence; couple outside a home; woman with baby on porch, undated; 00:00:00 - 00:04:12
    - 4th Session Oklahoma Business League honorary J. J. Simmon and Roscoe Dungee, Top Men, Muskogee, OK, 1927 July 8; 00:04:13 - 00:06:48
      Includes footage of a parade
    - One of Mr. and Mrs. J. H. Roberts farm homes, own 3,000 acres. R 2 Box 27 Bristow, OK, 1927; 00:06:49 -00:08:05
    - Farm home of Mr. and Mrs. J. Roberts, one of their oil wells, thousand acres, Bristow, OK, 1927 May 9; 00:08:06 - 00:09:12
    - Residence of Mr. and Mrs. C. C. Clayton, 228 Hobbson Street, Sapulpa, OK, 1927 May 9; 00:09:13 - 00:10:09
    - The Oklahoma Eagle Printing Company, a part of their office help, 117 North Greenwood Street, Tulsa, OK, 1927; 00:10:00 - 00:10:34
    - Resident of Mr. and Mrs. N. N. Minor, President of Hopewell District, W Con. and Reverend Gilfort Boswell, 1927 May 25; 00:10:35 - 00:12:13
    - Mr. and Mrs. J. Denmon home and property, 700 South Broadway, Hugo, OK, 1927 May 26; 00:12:14 - 00:13:20
      Includes funeral procession
    - Sunset Hotel and Add, Mr. J. B. Stamper, Owner and his K. V. Fox Trotter, Holdenville, OK, 1927 May 30; 00:13:21 - 00:14:58
    - Tulane Avenue Baptist Church Bus from New Orleans, Louisiana at General Convention Tulsa Brady Theater, Tulsa, OK, 1927; 00:14:59 - 00:17:15
      Procession of marching band entering the headquarters of the National Baptist [?] S. and B. Y. P. U. Congress and on the street
  - Film 3, 1926, undated; (487 feet) (Box 3 (Original))
    Shrinkage 1.1-1.7%%, 15 splices, a lot of ripped perforations, many folded edges, many torn frames, some tapes splices, thin and dense exposure.
    - People exiting church; people exiting a house; exterior of Ninth Street YMCA Branch, undated; 00:00:00 - 00:02:46
    - Winter scenes from train or automobile, undated; 00:02:47 - 00:03:32
    - Madam C. J. Walker's Million Dollar Management Company, 640 North West St., Mr. F. B. Ransom, Manager, Indianapolis, IN, 1926 January 9; 00:03:33 - 00:08:12
    - Mrs. Allace C. Burnett, National Representative Madam C .J Walker Co at S. W. headquarters, Muskogee, OK, 1926 January 16; 00:08:11 - 00:08:35
    - Corinthian Baptist Church and Sunday School Dr. Ira M. Hendon, Pastor, Indianapolis, IN, 1926 January 9; 00:08:36 - 00:10:45
    - Dr. and Mrs. Wesbrooks, a part of their great church on Sunday, Indianapolis, IN, 1926 January 19; 00:10:46 - 00:13:06
      People lined up outside of YMCA building
    - Home Mission Board National Baptist Convention, Ira M. Hendon, Secretary, Indianapolis, IN, 1926; 00:13:07 - 00:14:53
    - H. Parker house and livestock, Indianapolis, IN, 1926; 00:14:54 - 00:16:17
    - [C. J.] Walker Theatre, Indianapolis, IN, 1926; 00:16:18 - 00:17:51
  - Film 4, 1926-1927, undated; (456 feet) (Box 4 (Original))
    Shrinkage 1.1-1.3%, 27 splices, some torn frames, some ripped perforations, punctured sections by sprockets.
    - Woman outside in the snow, 1926; 00:00:00 - 00:00:13
    - St. James 2nd St. Baptist Church, Dr. J. H. Winn, Pastor, Indianapolis, IN, 1926 January 26; 00:00:14 - 00:00:50
    - Mt. Zion Baptist Church, few members J. W. Carter, Pastor, Denison, TX, 1927 February; 00:00:51 - 00:03:10
    - Few Baptist Pastors at Tulane Church, Dr. E. W. White Pastor, New Orleans, LA, 1927 February; 00:03:11 - 00:03:23
    - Madame Eva Ball White [Hair Care], 1109 Tulane Avenue, "Agents Wanted" New Orleans, LA, 1927 February; 00:03:24 - 00:05:08
    - Family on porch of residence, man drives away, undated; 00:05:09 - 00:05:33
    - Unidentified port and city, some footage from automobile or train, undated; 00:05:34 - 00:07:14
    - Fisk University, Jubilee Hall Nashville, TN, undated; 00:07:15 - 00:07:41
    - Mrs. P. Jones and a few of her children, the only sister of Dr. S. S. Jones of Muskogee, Memphis, TN, 1926 March 2; 00:07:42 -00:08:12
    - Orange Mound Embalming and Undertaking Co. Mr. Charles Jones, MRF, Memphis, TN, 1926 March 2; 00:08:13 - 00:09:13
    - Residence of Mother R. H. Boyd and daughter at their Nashville home, 1926 January 23; 00:09:14 - 00:09:39
    - Mr. and Mrs. A. J. Harrison Plaster Contractor, 753 Cella Street, Orange Mound, Memphis, TN "Write him", 1926 June 21; 00:09:40 - 00:10:43
    - Mt. Mariah Baptist Congregation, Dr. A. D. Bell, Pastor Orange Mound, Memphis, TN, 1926 June 20; 00:10:44 - 00:12:47
    - Mr. and Mrs. William Davis and family 24[6]3 Saratoga Street, Orange Mound, Memphis, TN, 1926 June 20; 00:12:48 - 00:14:26
    - Mr. and Mrs. Herbert Gray, she waits on Bosys, 2453 Carnes Avenue, Orange Mound, Memphis, TN, 1926 June 20; 00:14:27 - 00:15:14
    - Residence of Mrs. Vinnie Owens 2451 Carnes Avenue, Orange Mound, Memphis, TN, 1926 June 20; 00:15:15 - 00:15:30
    - Mr. and Mrs. Ben Bullard Contractors and Builders, 42 houses going Up 1406 LaMarr Boulevard, Memphis, TN "Write him", 1926 June 21; 00:15:31 -00:16:40
  - Film 5, 1925-1926, undated; (358 feet) (Box 5 (Original))
    Shrinkage 1.2-1.55%, 15 splices, some ripped perforations, several sections pulled perforations.
    - The sun lights the world for $200 per year 2008 Broadway, Gary, IN, undated; 00:00:00 - 00:00:08
    - Mrs. Z .H. Bagby, Editor of the Sun, Gary, IN; appointing AGT S in Okmulgee, OK, 1925 November 31; 00:00:09 - 00:01:00
    - Turkey Day MTH Muskogee vs. BWH of Tulsa Parade, Muskogee, OK, 1925 November 26; 00:01:01 -00:02:29
    - Football game, 1925 November 26; 00:02:30 - 00:06:51
    - The Muskogee Symphony Band, Thanksgiving, 1925 November 26; 00:06:52 -00:07:18
    - The End, MTH Muskogee 9, BWH Tulsa 13, Professor Sadler and Brooks, 1925 November 26; 00:07:19 -00:07:23
    - Dr. Roberson of Arkensas showing Dr. Bennett PA one of his Black Farms near Little Rock, AR, 1925 November 16; 00:07:24 -00:08:48
    - The Union Industrial and Grit College Dr. Roberson Leader near Little Rock, AR, 1925 November 16; 00:08:49 - 00:09:00
    - School children exiting and entering a school house, undated; 00:09:01 - 00:09:59
    - Mrs. Mary Troutt creek rooms its home like [630] 4th Street, Okmulgee, OK, 1925 November 31; 00:10:00 -00:10:39
    - The Oklahoma Colored Hospital Association and a few officers and members and friends, Okmulgee, OK, 1925 November 21; 00:10:40 - 00:11:56
    - Unidentified family at their residence, woman getting her hair done, undated; 00:11:57 - 00:13:22
    - Mrs. E. Polk Ingram 1[8] North Compton St. Louis, MO on her Around the World Campaign, 1926 July 16; 00:13:23 - 00:14:08
    - Mrs. Beulam Bowles model hair culture she manufactures her goods, agents wanted, England, AK, 1926 July 26; 00:14:09 - 00:14:16
  - Film 6, 1926, undated; (430 feet) (Box 6 (Original))
    Shrinkage1.35-1.6%, 25 splices, few torn frames, open splices, some ripped perforations.
    - President I. W. Young of Langston talks to Muskogee teachers Professor S. L. Sadler Pri, speaks at Church Antioch Muskogee, OK, 1926 March 27; 00:00:00 - 00:01:26
    - Train scene "Rock Island" El Reno station, undated; 00:01:27 - 00:02:02
    - Another one out, auto collision at 12th and Fondulac, Muskogee, OK, 1926 April 9; 00:02:03 -00:02:20
    - Creek Co. Training School, Mr. and Mrs. T. W. Grissom, Mrs. C. L. Roberts, Harlinville, OK, 1926 February 24; 00:02:21 - 00:03:39
    - Antioch Cadets with Mrs. Ragsdale and L. Davis, Leaders off for hike, Muskogee, OK, 1926 February 26; 00:03:40 -00:04:04
    - Douglas Ward School, Professor D. M. Lewis and faculty and students, Muskogee, OK, 1926 January 14; 00:04:05 -00:07:13
    - Mr. T. J. Elliott, 43rd, (Elliot Furnishings, Clothing and Shoes) Annual Spring style Show. (Elliott sold all Stetson Hats in Eastern Oklahoma, so whites had to even buy from him in E. Oklahoma (franchise) A Dapper Show), Muskogee, OK, 1926 March 15; 00:07:14 - 00:11:40
    - A part of Elliott's store organization Monday morning, Muskogee, OK, 1926 March 15; 00:11:41 - 00:13:03
      Fashion show footage
    - Mr. and Mrs. Ben Canady farm home 5 miles north of Depew, OK, 1926 February 24; 00:13:04 - 00:14:19
    - Oklahoma Boy Prisoners being transferred to Boley from McAlister, OK, 1926 March 9; 00:14:20 - 00:15:59
  - Film 7, undated; (417 feet) (Box 7 (Original))
    Shrinkage 1.6-1.7%, 27 splices, many ripped perforations, several torn frames, some burned frames, several sections pulled perforations about 70 ft completely unusable.
    - Passengers leaving ship, England, 00:00:00 - 00:00:52
    - City footage (Paris?), 00:00:53 - 00:01:38
    - In Paris France Republican guards on duty, 00:01:39 - 00:01:54
    - Eiffel tower and Grand Boulevard in Paris, 00:01:55 - 00:02:23
    - Zanever Leads Napoleon's Tomb, 00:02:24 - 00:02:43
    - King's Palace in Versailles, greatest in the world, the glory of Louis XIV, 00:02:44 - 00:03:33
    - Church shelled by the Germans, Paris, France, 00:03:34 - 00:04:04
    - Battle Field France, 108 Hill, 00:04:05 - 00:04:34
    - Ship dock in Marseilles, France, 00:04:35 - 00:04:56
    - Street scenes in Marseilles, 00:04:57 - 00:05:57
    - Flower sellers in Paris, 00:05:58 - 00:06:12
    - Corner at Notre Dame in Paris, 00:06:13 - 00:06:43
    - Loading our baggage for English Channel, 00:06:44 - 00:07:10
    - Thomas Gray's Tomb, England, 00:07:11 - 00:07:23
    - The King's Royal Guards at Buckingham Palace London, 00:07:24 - 00:08:16
    - Queen Victoria's Monument, 00:08:17 - 00:08:53
    - The King's SuMadamr Palace in Windsor, 00:08:54 - 00:08:42
    - Center Hampton Pool Court, 00:08:43 - 00:11:21
    - Fast train for London, 00:11:22 - 00:11:41
    - Dock scene Liverpool, 00:11:42 - 00:12:17
    - On SS Baltic, Farewell Liverpool, 00:12:18 - 00:13:18
    - Queen's Town Ireland from the big ship Big Ship Form, 00:13:19 - 00:14:13
    - Irish silk sellers and sea gulls, 00:14:14 -00:14:55
    - Big ship from Queen's town, in life preservers on our ship, 00:14:56 - 00:15:32
  - Film 8, 1925, 1927, undated; (386 feet) (Box 8 (Original))
    Shrinkage 1.2-1.4%, 18 splices, many ripped perforations, several sections torn off perforation.
    - Willow Grove District 8, Memphis, TN, undated; 00:00:00 - 00:02:59
      Kids exercising, dancing
    - Big Church Program Memphis, TN, undated; 00:03:00 - 00:04:51
    - 1st Battalion, 1st FA.; 3rd Battalion, 20th Inf.,44th Obs., Squadron AC, undated; 00:04:52 - 00:05:42
    - Antioch Baptist Church, a few officers and members, Reverend C.A. Hinton, Pastor, Duncan, OK, 1927 April 29; 00:05:44 - 00:05:39
    - Armstead Grocery and Market Filling Station in trade South 4th Street, Duncan, OK, 1927 April 29; 00:05:40 - 00:07:30
    - Mr. L.C. Murphy and family on his cannon bottom farm 8 miles from Okemah, OK, 1925 December 19; 00:07:31 -00:08:29
    - Boley Grade and High School from 1st to 12th grades and teachers, Professor C. B. Bryant, Principal, Boley, OK, 1925 December 19; 00:08:30 - 00:11:09
    - Annual Stock Holder Meeting, S. D. Hooker Dry Goods Co. with Mr. Hunter of PA and Mr. Rody of TN, 1925 December 29; 00:11:10 - 00:14:30
  - Film 9, 1925-1926, undated; (255 feet) (Box 9 (Original))
    Shrinkage 1.65-1.9%, 20 splices, some sections broken off perforation.
    - Funeral march, undated; 00:00:00 - 00:01:05
    - Residence of Mr. and Mrs. P. J. Nichols, 718 North 5th, Muskogee, OK, 1926 June 26; 00:01:06 - 00:01:49
    - Residence of Mr. and Mrs. A. Poole and two friends, 1101 North 3rd St. Muskogee, OK, 1926 June 26; 00:01:50 - 00:02:56
    - Residence of Mrs. Luther Manual, Brother and Sisters, some of Mrs. Luther Manual cattle and stock, Muskogee, OK, 1925 December 10; 00:02:57 - 00:04:17
    - Baby Jane V. and the Manual off for the city [18] mile house pony, 1925 December 10; 00:04:18 - 00:04:21
    - School children, undated; 00:05:22 -00:06:34
    - Mr. A.W. Marchell and Sons, contractors finishing, Baptist Church at Taft, OK, 1925 December 19; 00:06:35 - 00:07:15
    - City Drug Store, 521 East 5th St., C. P. Wallace, Okmulgee, OK, 1925 December 19; 00:07:17 - 00:08:58
    - Antioch Baptist Church, singers at dinner in Sever Hotel after singing for guests, Christmas, Muskogee, OK, 1925 December 25; 00:08:59 - 00:09:41
  - Film 10, 1925; (392 feet) (Box 10 (Original))
    Shrinkage 1.5-2.4%, 42 splices, many ripped perforations, some sections broken off perforations, several punctured sections.
    - Dr. R.H. Boyd picture, National Baptist Publishing Board Baptist Headquarters, Nashville, TN, 1925 [June 21]; 00:00:00 - 00:00:55
    - Bird's-eye view of S. S. Congress and Dept Bldg, Beaumont, TX, 1925 June; 00:00:56 - 00:01:58
    - S. S. Congress 5000 on the inside Dr. M. E. Roberson Ch., Beaumont, TX, 1925 June; 00:01:59 - 00:02:26
    - Dr. and Mrs. J. W. Hurse of Kansas City, Missouri and Mrs. Ashburn, Beaumont, TX, 1925 June; 00:02:27 - 00:03:00
    - AF Cadets Boy Department, Beaumont, TX, 1925 June; 00:03:01 - 00:04:30
    - Advance Teachers and Home Departmental Buildings, Beaumont, TX, 1925 June; 00:04:31 - 00:04:42
    - Dr. H. A. Boyd his mother and sister at S. S. Congress, Beaumont, TX, 1925 June; 00:04:44 - 00:05:01
    - Mr. Ashburn of Chicago, IL and some National Women at S. S. Congress, Beaumont, TX, 1925 June; 00:05:02 - 00:05:56
    - Dr. J. P. Roberson, Chairman of the National Publication Board and Drs. Over and Hall of the Bible Dept., Beaumont, TX, 1925 June; 00:05:57 - 00:06:21
    - Local Com. Dr. M. E. Robinson, Chairman, Professor Pollard, Eugene Barton, Price and others, Beaumont, TX, 1925 June; 00:06:22 - 00:06:42
    - Music Department Miss R. L. Carpenter, Conductor, Beaumont, TX, 1925 June; 00:06:43 - 00:07:08
    - Metoka and Galedas, Superintendents Department, Beaumont, TX, 1925 June; 00:07:09 - 00:09:04
    - B. Y. P. U. Department, Beaumont, TX, 1925 June; 00:09:05 - 00:11:12
    - Layman's League Professor McCorklee and Johnson Leaders, Beaumont, TX, 1925 June; 00:11:13 - 00:12:00
    - National S. S. Congress Parade on Magnolia St. Sunday, "Juneteenth" Beaumont, TX, 1925 June14; 00:12:01 - 00:14:33
  - Film 11, 1925, undated; (390 feet) (Box 11 (Original))
    Shrinkage 1.6-1.8%, 15 splices, several ripped perforations.
    - Native Americans in full dress, undated; 00:00:00 - 00:01:53
    - Peoples Hotel and Café Leading in the City, 316 North 2nd St, North Fuller, Owner, Muskogee, OK, 1925 August 4; 00:01:54 - 00:02:19
    - Residence of Attorney H. T. Walker and Family, 24th and Findlay Street, Muskogee, OK, undated; 00:02:20 - 00:02:46
      A shot shows the slate hanging on the front of the house
    - Residence of Reverend and Mrs. William Stevenson, 505 Katy Avenue, Muskogee, OK, 1925 August 5; 00:02:47 - 00:03:23
    - Little Ruby Wise, 8 years old, near Haskell Oklahoma, piece of arm bitten of by horse, 1925 August 7; 00:03:24 - 00:03:42
    - Residence of Reverend and Mrs. F.A. Murdock, 621 Howard Street, Muskogee, OK, 1925 August 9; 00:03:43 - 00:04:15
    - Residence of Mr. and Mrs. J. F. Burton, 629 North 13th Street, Muskogee, OK, 1925 August 1; 00:04:16 - 00:04:46
    - Interior of Hon. R. Emmit Stewart's Office, Elliott Building, 111 South 2nd Street, Muskogee, OK, 1925 August 1; 00:04:47 - 00:05:15
    - His Stenographer and Law Partner, M. R. Smith, Muskogee, OK, 1925 August 1; 00:05:16 - 00:05:57
    - Residence of Mr. and Mrs. T. J. Elliott, 301 North 11th Street, Muskogee, OK, 1925 August 1; 00:05:58 - 00:06:17
    - Residence of Mr. and Mrs. S. L. Sadler, 305 North 11th Street, Muskogee, OK, 1925 August 1; 00:06:18 - 00:06:48
    - Residence of Dr. and Mrs. L.S. Wilson, 325 North 11th Street, Muskogee, OK, 1925 August 1; 00:06:49 - 00:07:16
    - The Home Undertaking Co., 20 years experience, Corner 2nd and Denison, Muskogee, OK, 1925 August 3; 00:07:17 - 00:07:43
    - Home Undertaking Co. Ambulance Service, Ragsdale and Sons, Muskogee, OK, 1925 August 3; 00:07:44 - 00:08:14
      Includes footage of someone being brought out of a house on a stretcher and put in an ambulance
    - Residence of Mr. and Mrs. Weathersby, 814 South 3rd Street, For Sale Wright US, Muskogee, OK, 1925 August; 00:08:15 - 00:08:43
    - Residence of Mr. and Mrs. John L. Evans, 14th and Hartford Street, Muskogee, OK, 1925 August 3; 00:08:44 - 00:09:16
    - Residence of Mr. and Mrs. N. J. Elliott, 627 South 2nd Street, Muskogee, OK, 1925 August 4; 00:09:17 - 00:09:51
    - Residence of Mr. and Mrs. William Mayers, 615 Fremont Street, Muskogee, OK, 1925 August 4; 00:09:52 - 00:10:10
    - Residence of Mrs. Grace Posey, 502 Fondulac Street, Muskogee, OK, 1925 August 4; 00:10:11 - 00:10:24
    - Residence of Mr. and Mrs. R. E. Stewart, 905 Market Street, Muskogee, OK, 1925 August 1; 00:10:25 - 00:11:01
      Slate hanging on side of tree